You gotta pay the troll toll
The Toll is a thriller, horror film directed by Michael Nader.
A socially awkward driver and a weary passenger try to make it to their
destination while being haunted by a supernatural threat.
Cami, played by Jordan Hayes.
Spencer, played by Max Topplin.
Neil, played by James McGowan.
Lorraine, played by Rosemary Dunsmore.
Weston, played by Thomas L. Colford.
Andrea, played by Sharon McFarlane.
The Toll is a 2020 Canadian horror thriller film directed by Michael Nader.
The film stars Jordan Hayes and Max Topplin, with James
McGowan and Rosemary Dunsmore in supporting roles.
It follows a young woman (Hayes) who, after hailing a late-night ride-share, finds herself trapped with a strange driver
(Topplin) on a deserted road, as the two become targets of a mysterious and malevolent force known as "The Toll Man".
The Toll premiered at the 2020 Bucheon International Fantastic Film
Festival and the South by Southwest Film Festival.
This was followed by a limited release and later became available on video on demand
platforms due to the COVID-19 pandemic, which impacted its wider theatrical release.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, with the performances of Hayes and Topplin
receiving praise, while its screenplay and pacing received criticism.
The film explores themes of supernatural, trauma, bow
and arrow, lost in the woods, toll.
The tone is dark and intense.